[MUSIC PLAYING ON TV]
Yeah, I'm sorry, but I'm not going to watch
the Clone Wars TV series...
(Sheldon:)...until I've seen the Clone Wars movie.
(Sheldon:)I prefer to let George Lucas disappoint me
in the order he intended.
Well, I wanna watch it now.
(Sheldon:)Then I believe we've arrived...
...at another quintessential Rock, Paper,
Scissors, Lizard, Spock moment.
(Leonard:)Watch whatever you want.
(Raj:)I saw what you did there.
What'd I do?
[PHONE RINGS]
Hello? Hey, Howard.
(Leonard(answering phone):)What's wrong?
Uh, okay. Okay, we'll be right there.
- What happened?
- Howard's at the Mars-rover lab.
(Leonard:)He says he's in trouble. DEFCON 5.
(Sheldon:)DEFCON 5? Well, there's no need to rush.
(Girl:)- What?
- DEFCON 5 means no danger.